miamimusicweek.com 2018-08-22

# Privacy Policy | Miami Music Week

__  

This Privacy Policy Statement (“Privacy Policy”) describes the types of personal information that Miami Music Week collects via the website (the “MMW Website”), and how the personal information is protected, used and shared. This Privacy Policy only governs the collection of information through the MMW Website and does not govern the collection of any personal information through any third party websites, or any other means.

## Collection and Use of Information

The MMW Website does not collect any personal information, unless such information is voluntarily provided. Such information that may be collected includes name, email address, gender, birthday and country of residence from visitors who join the email list. The MMW Website uses personal information collected to respond to your inquiries and for any other purposes for which you have provided such personal information.

The MMW Website server automatically recognizes and collects certain information about, and from, visitors, including IP address, web browser type, web browser version, address of the website from which you entered the MMW Website and date and time of access. This information is used only to improve and optimize the content of the MMW Website. We may share information that is not personally identifiable with third parties who provide us statistical information about the use of the MMW Website.

Personal information collected through the MMW Website is not shared, sold or rented, except as described within this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

Temporary, session-specific cookies may be used to track the MMW Website traffic. Cookies do not: (i) reveal or contain any identifying or personal data; (ii) cannot read any information on your computer; and (iii) cannot interact with other cookies on your hard drive. Cookies stay on the user’s hard drive to identify site visits and whether the user is a returning visitor.

## Security

The MMW Website undertakes reasonable security measures to protect the information that is collected. While security of personally identifiable information is a top priority, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to the MMW Website.

The server does not record or collect e-mail addresses.

## Third Party Websites

For your convenience, the MMW Website may contain links to external websites. Such websites are neither endorsed by the MMW Website nor is the MMW Website responsible for the content, accuracy or privacy practices of such websites.

## Modifications

This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time without prior notice to users. If any significant changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will notify users via a notice on the home page of the MMW Website.

## Contact

If you have any questions or comments about these Terms and Conditions, please email us at [info@miamimusicweek.com](mailto:info@miamimusicweek.com).
